{
	"cards": [
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-22-tag-multiple-choice-card-1",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"The Salmonella bacterium itself causes food poisoning.",
					"Refrigeration of food will prevent salmonellosis.",
					"The Salmonella bacterium produces toxins that cause food poisoning.",
					"Symptoms of salmonellosis appear within 12 hours."
				],
				"question": "Which of the following statements regarding the Salmonella bacterium is correct?",
				"source": "See Food Poisoning"
			},
			"back": "The Salmonella bacterium itself causes food poisoning."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-22-tag-multiple-choice-card-2",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"How long ago was the substance taken?",
					"Why was the substance ingested?",
					"What type of substance was taken?",
					"How much of the substance was taken?"
				],
				"question": "Which of the following questions would be least pertinent during the initial questioning of a patient who ingested a substance?",
				"source": "See Identifying the Patient and the Poison"
			},
			"back": "Why was the substance ingested?"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-22-tag-multiple-choice-card-3",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"avoid contaminating yourself.",
					"obtain and maintain a patent airway.",
					"decontaminate the patient’s skin.",
					"move the patient to a safe area."
				],
				"question": "Your priority in caring for a patient with a surface contact poisoning is to:",
				"source": "See How Poisons Enter the Body"
			},
			"back": "avoid contaminating yourself."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-22-tag-multiple-choice-card-4",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"ibuprofen.",
					"acetaminophen.",
					"aspirin.",
					"cocaine."
				],
				"question": "A patient who presents with rapid breathing, nausea and vomiting, ringing in the ears, and hyperthermia should be suspected of ingesting a significant quantity of:",
				"source": "See Specific Poisons"
			},
			"back": "aspirin."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-22-tag-multiple-choice-card-5",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"try to find the container the substance was in.",
					"administer naloxone via the intranasal route.",
					"keep the patient supine and elevate his legs.",
					"encourage the patient to drink milk or water."
				],
				"question": "If you are uncertain how to treat a patient who has been poisoned or exposed to a specific substance, you should:",
				"source": "See How Poisons Enter the Body"
			},
			"back": "try to find the container the substance was in."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-22-tag-multiple-choice-card-6",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"dependence.",
					"withdrawal.",
					"addiction.",
					"tolerance."
				],
				"question": "A person who routinely misuses a substance and requires increasing amounts to achieve the same effect is experiencing:",
				"source": "See Specific Poisons"
			},
			"back": "tolerance."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-22-tag-multiple-choice-card-7",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"call medical control.",
					"monitor the patient’s blood pressure.",
					"document the intervention.",
					"be alert for vomiting."
				],
				"question": "After administering activated charcoal to a patient, it is most important to:",
				"source": "See Emergency Medical Care"
			},
			"back": "be alert for vomiting."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-22-tag-multiple-choice-card-8",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"knows why the patient overdosed on the drug.",
					"is aware of the substance that is involved.",
					"knows the location of the closest hospital.",
					"is aware of the patient’s age and gender."
				],
				"question": "The poison control center will provide you with the most information regarding the appropriate treatment for a patient with a drug overdose if the center:",
				"source": "See How Poisons Enter the Body"
			},
			"back": "is aware of the substance that is involved."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-22-tag-multiple-choice-card-9",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"black stools.",
					"abdominal pain.",
					"headache.",
					"ringing in the ears."
				],
				"question": "The major side effect associated with administration of activated charcoal is:",
				"source": "See Emergency Medical Care"
			},
			"back": "black stools."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-22-tag-multiple-choice-card-10",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Injected poison.",
					"Plant poisoning.",
					"Alkaline poison.",
					"Inhaled poison."
				],
				"question": "What type of poisoning will cause burns around the mouth in children?",
				"source": "See How Poisons Enter the Body"
			},
			"back": "Alkaline poison."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-22-tag-multiple-choice-card-11",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"InstaChar.",
					"Fructose.",
					"Actidose.",
					"LiquiChar."
				],
				"question": "Common names for activated charcoal include all of the following, except:",
				"source": "See Emergency Medical Care"
			},
			"back": "Fructose."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-22-tag-multiple-choice-card-12",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"crack cocaine.",
					"oxycodone (Percocet).",
					"ecstasy.",
					"amphetamine sulfate (Benzedrine)."
				],
				"question": "Hypotension, hypoventilation, and pinpoint pupils would be expected following an overdose of:",
				"source": "See Specific Poisons"
			},
			"back": "oxycodone (Percocet)."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-22-tag-multiple-choice-card-13",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"injection",
					"inhalation",
					"absorption",
					"ingestion"
				],
				"question": "Most poisonings occur via the __________ route.",
				"source": "See How Poisons Enter the Body"
			},
			"back": "ingestion"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-22-tag-multiple-choice-card-14",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"sympathomimetic.",
					"hypnotic.",
					"cholinergic.",
					"opioid."
				],
				"question": "Heroin is an example of a(n):",
				"source": "See Specific Poisons"
			},
			"back": "opioid."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-22-tag-multiple-choice-card-15",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"recognize that a poisoning occurred.",
					"administer the appropriate antidote.",
					"contact poison control immediately.",
					"administer 25 g of activated charcoal."
				],
				"question": "An EMT’s primary responsibility to the patient who has been poisoned is to:",
				"source": "See Identifying the Patient and the Poison"
			},
			"back": "recognize that a poisoning occurred."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-22-tag-multiple-choice-card-16",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"tachycardia.",
					"hypotension.",
					"slurred speech.",
					"hypothermia."
				],
				"question": "Signs and symptoms of a sympathomimetic drug overdose include:",
				"source": "See Specific Poisons"
			},
			"back": "tachycardia."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-22-tag-multiple-choice-card-17",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"methanol.",
					"ethanol.",
					"aspirin.",
					"iron."
				],
				"question": "Activated charcoal may be indicated for a patient who ingested:",
				"source": "See Emergency Medical Care"
			},
			"back": "aspirin."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-22-tag-multiple-choice-card-18",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"increases the senses.",
					"induces sleep.",
					"increases the pulse.",
					"prevents amnesia."
				],
				"question": "A hypnotic drug is one that:",
				"source": "See Specific Poisons"
			},
			"back": "induces sleep."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-22-tag-multiple-choice-card-19",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"an alkaline antidote.",
					"activated charcoal.",
					"oxygen.",
					"syrup of ipecac."
				],
				"question": "Airborne substances should be diluted with:",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment"
			},
			"back": "oxygen."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-22-tag-multiple-choice-card-20",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"knowingly selling illicit drugs to buy more drugs.",
					"misusing a substance to produce a desired effect.",
					"unwillingly and unknowingly consuming drugs or alcohol.",
					"willfully using a therapeutic drug to treat a medical illness."
				],
				"question": "Substance abuse is most accurately defined as:",
				"source": "See Identifying the Patient and the Poison"
			},
			"back": "misusing a substance to produce a desired effect."
		}
	],
	"category": {
		"value": "chapter-22",
		"label": "Chapter 22"
	},
	"tags": [
		{
			"value": "multiple-choice",
			"label": "Multiple Choice"
		}
	]
}